hello hi what's your name my name is
Kevin Lee hi Kevin where you from I'm
from Los
Angeles
go how old are you I'm 25 what is your
talent what do you do I do
magic we love magic then you must be in
the right place cuz magic is Magic on
this show y a GT I grew up watching this
show with my family and to help Bond us
to help connect us and I hope I can
share the same Joy with other families
watching well I wish you the best of
luck go ahead young man thank
you it's thought that we each have a set
of core memories that Define who we are
of course photos help capture these
memories judges I have a few photos of
us here Simon Heidi Sophia hoe Terry and
myself to help take a mental snapshot of
this moment right
here we share a lot of the same core
memories mostly from our childhood like
pulling your first all
nighter your first
crush these images represent core
Memories We tend to all experience let's
unlock some of them together now hi
Heidi hello I'd like you to take out one
of these pictures for me yes they were
all different don't look at it just yet
okay Heidi I'm going to close my eyes
can you show the photo to everybody show
the judges show the
world and when you're done Heidi hide
the photo put it
away and everyone just do your best to
vividly remember all the details of
about it
yes Heidi hold out your index finger for
me this is going to help out a lot okay
go like
this ET phone
home I'm seeing a screen not a small
screen like a phone this is
larger I'm smelling something buttery wa
judges in the photo are you all eating
popcorn at the movie
theater
no Sophia can you pretend you're placing
a piece of popcorn on my
head oh that's a popcorn
konel watch closely don't
[Music]
blink oh no oh
no good thing that wasn't
[Music]
popped Simon what do you see inside the
Box
nothing we'll take the konel place it
inside
and heat it up a
[Music]
bit can you cup your hands for
me
wow
we tend to focus a lot on the future
that sometimes we forget about all the
memories that made us who we are today
let's rewind the hands of time even more
judges let's all go
[Music]
back wa a it's us look how cute you all
are even
Simon
these kids especially me would have
never dreamed we'd all be here together
this memory we made here tonight will
forever be a part of us and I am just
forever grateful thank
[Music]
you I love it I got
[Applause]
HB Heidi I love your magic I love your
magic I love
you but I have to say my favorite was
when this colonel was coming out of your
eyeball I mean it was like it was kind
of disgusting but it was so cool I loved
it thank you
Sophia you know it's amazing to see you
now so emotional because when you were
doing your show you were so in control
you look like you were like so present
everything it was spectacular thank
you Simon you're just good and you're
cool and you're
different we've seen a lot of magic over
the years but you did something
different I could tell how much this
means to you you which I think is
amazing and you're slick and you're
Vagas and you're very us and I really
like
you thank you Simon thank you thank you
you know the story that you tell the
image of a little boy sitting in his
home with his family and his parents
watching America's Got Talent and then
years later not only being on that spot
that you watched But Rising to the
occasion and Rising above that occasion
I think you just had a career and
lifechanging performance thank you let's
vote it's a yes for me idy it's a yes
for me Sophia yes you now have four
yeses let's
go
W thank
[Applause]
you I love it
kin
[Music]
Lee man come here give me a h but that
thing with the eye thing with the eye
was crazy it was so nasty I loved it
yeah I was scared there was going to be
popcorn come out of your
eyes next time I love you I love you
Kevin
wow
hi what is your name my name is my name
is Bren Cummings and I'm a vist
a many how old are you um I'm 12 where
are you from uh we're from Papa
Michigan how did you get into doing this
how did you know you could do this um
well it was actually I remember seeing
Darcy Lynn on AGT and that um inspired
me I literally looked at my parents as
soon as I saw and I went that's what I'm
going to do
so and look at you now right here in
front of us that's amazing what are you
going to do if you win $1 million I mean
it's a big thing but probably I'd like
to follow and Darcy's footsteps and uh
start touring uh so get like a tour bus
and I also really want a bearded dragon
oh wow okay we're ready go
ahead all right penel it's our big
moment are you ready for me to cue the
music I don't want to sing anr what this
is what we've practiced for weeks I've
been thinking about it and it's then
done they want to see something else
something
new but we haven't practiced anything
else what's your plan I've got it
mentalism mentalism wait
what I don't mind Reed quit playing
around let's just sing the song trust me
take me down to the judges is that
allowed yeah sure
yeah so good I have a bad feeling about
this oh stop worrying seriously I don't
know what I'm supposed to do it's okay
we'll use a deck of cards check your
tet wait what
taada Heidi I'd like you to cut the deck
one
time
Howie I'd like you to take the top card
all right thenen look away and close
your eyes show me the card I will send
my thoughts to D using thy Brilliance
and dental
Powers what do I do now just concentrate
what comes to mind a migraine
th okay I'm Focus I see I think it's
black that's it keep thinking it's a
club is it the seven of clubs open in
your eyes oh my
gosh what that's
amazing that's crazy judges in a moment
we're going to go back on stage but as
we do Sophia hi please take out any item
from The Thirst the keep it hidden for
now okay sign in please turn now into
the audience and grab an object any
object suround the anyone yep in the
audience
and judges don't let us see what you
picked do not let us see what you
[Applause]
pick let's make this a little more
interesting Terry can you bring out the
blindfold
blindfolds Terry Inu the blindfold hold
it up to the lights can you see through
it no I can't perfect please put it on
the r okay make it make it nice and
tight nice and tight perfect perfect
thank you Terry you can go you can leave
now thank you so much you're going to
figure out what objects the judges are
holding sopia hold your object up into
the air D clear your
mind so what do you see I see it's a
food um it might be it has some sugar in
it um it might be like a good treat
maybe you leave it when Santa comes is
it a cookie Sophia what was your object
it's a no F
cookie oh my gosh since you doing so
well you're going to try this one solo
penelopee come on I need your help fine
here's a
clue sign in object can fit inside of
this room Penelope
come on wait wait I'm getting something
it's it's an accessory um you might wear
it on your ank no you wear on your wrist
uh is it an Apple Watch uh
yes wow oh my
gosh
wow thank you
everyone that's
amazing
yay green you are adorable thank you it
was so much fun it's so great to see you
ride up closeth how good you're doing it
I loved it thank you so much this is the
season of mashups the fact that you did
Magic or mentalism and ventriloquism at
the same time you're amazing young lady
thank you so much yes
yes
I loved it too because you really
figured out like a perfect little act
for yourself you're part comedian too I
thought it was a lot of fun well done
thank you so
much when did you realize that you have
magic powers um when I was about 9 years
old I would say that's cool you are so
talented so Charming people are going to
root for you you did something we've
never seen before and for me you never
want to see the same thing again but not
quite as good you want to see it better
or different and that's what you did
thank you okay we're going to vote
Sophia I'm going to give you your first
yes second yes third yes four
yeses she did it she did
it
oh my God oh my
goodness
oh so oh my goodness BR tell me how
you're feeling right now this is the
best moment of my life oh that's so
beautiful thank you good evening hello
hello who are you beautiful girl I'm
Mandy Mandy muden I'm from London in a
United Kingdom how old are you
uh I'm 29 oh it's been a rough couple of
years you know what I
[Laughter]
mean and uh what do you do Mandy um I do
magic why AGT now well being British as
Simon will back me up to say I love
America also I owe money and that to get
out of the
UK what are you going to do with a min
dollar if you win well I do I'd probably
spend it on men on
men okay we're ready for you we want to
see your magic okay
fantastic right everybody are you ready
to get into a magic
mood okay America's Got
Talent look at this for strangers ready
to judge me it's like one of those
parties where you throw the car keys
into the
Fishbowl
heidy would you just I've got a bag here
full of letters could you just reach in
and get a few out just to make sure that
they're all different it's very
difficult with the glov son isn't it if
you just committed a crime and hoping to
get away with
it they all look different lovely shove
that back I'll give the bag a bit of a
shake hi Howie I I want you just to take
a letter um don't look at it okay okay
fantastic could you take one as well
take it out yes please and don't look at
it we'll come back to that later okay
Sophia could you do the
same okay fantastic now Simon I'm going
to riffle through my book could you just
stick anything in you
[Applause]
like finger yes a finger would be lovely
Simon Okay brilliant now Simon could you
look at the page number yes and the
first word on the page Simon got it okay
and could you write them down and
remember them yes I can okay fantastic
I'm just going to pop back up to the
stage feel free to check me out Simon
okay right here we go now hoe I want you
to think of any word at all in the
English language okay now would you be
impressed if the word you were thinking
of was written on a piece of paper in
the bag in front of you yes more than
impressed please open the
bag it's a
dictionary
unbelievable Heidi and Sophia open your
packages okay Heidi what lovely love
story do you have Heidi mine says 50
Shades of Gray oh now Simon what page
were you on 70 okay Heidi could you turn
to page 70 I'm just going to go go into
a trance and read your mind here we
go page
70 does your word begin with an F yes
right lovely now are you familiar with
this word yes I'm familiar with the word
okay oh my God now the spirits are
telling me that this word ends in i n g
okay have you done this word
today
[Applause]
yes that's my girl
fantastic is your word by any chance is
it um
fantasizing yes it
is okay now Sophia could you go to 70
could you look at the last word on PTI I
don't have my
glasses
170 okay how you've got dictionary there
yes could you go to page
330 okay and could you go down seven
word entries seven words one 2 3 4 5 6 7
what's the word Looney
no it's
[Applause]
lone now Simon you were thinking of a
word you wrote it down what was your
word eat eat how you picked a letter did
you hold your letter up and shout out
it's it's an e an e what do you have
there Heidi I have an A and what do you
have Sophia a t
unbelievable thank you so
much oh wow thank you so much thank you
Mandy that was quite a surprise oh
you're so funny and and I didn't expect
to have so much
fun Howie you're a very good magician
you're funny I love you I'm a huge fan
of yours you are the epitome of somebody
that deserves to have their own show I
would go see just you in Las Vegas oh
wow thank you so much thank you II I
think that you are adorable and can I
keep this yes of course
Dion we saw everything didn't we I mean
you were Min reading you were funny
you're very
naughty I really like you oh thank you I
do so we're going to vote Heidi it's a
yes for me for Mandy oh thank you so
much s it's it's a yes Howe three
yeses
yes thank you so much that's amazing
[Applause]
thank you thank
you she is really good I'm absolutely in
shocked that was amazing I couldn't
believe what Howe said it it was like
he's such a hero of mine I was like oh
my God she is great thank you thank you
so much celebrate thank you thank
you hi hello welcome welcome welcome
what is your name uh my name my name is
Ryland how old are you I'm 10 years old
and uh where are you from I'm from
England uh so Ryland okay oh yes yes yes
yes yes he yes yes he's from England we
know um what is your talent young man uh
well I'm a magician oo
wow how long you've been doing that
since I was two so eight years wow two
um so uh I was I was born with magical
powers and my dad's uh is a magician and
he gave me some of the magical powers
that he didn't need anymore
wow okay and what about the million
dollars if you get it what would you do
with that I'll give some to my mom my
sister and my dad and spend the rest on
Legos
okay okay let's see what you've got
tonight
thank you tonight I would like you to
help me create a brand new magic word a
magic word but first I have gifts you
see I love drawing and coloring in and
I've drawn you each of picture to look
at later this one's for you hoe all
right this one's for you Heidi thank you
this one's for you Sophia and this one's
for you Simon now don't peek inside the
envelopes don't let anyone else touch
them we'll get back to them
later what you about to see is amazing
but I can't do it on my own I need help
luckily I have lots of friends that love
magic just like me oh hello
there hi friends we got a lot of
friends I'll let each of you to pick one
of my friends pick one of the numbers
and I'll place it in this
holder you get to choose which position
it goes in there are multiple
combinations and the choices are all
yours we'll start with you H please name
one of my friends me uh okay uh
Mark and would you like the number seven
or 23 I'll take seven it's lucky and
where would you like it to go 1 2 3 or
four first cuz I'm first okay so number
one hey it's your turn I choose om would
you like 11 or 26 11 and where would you
like that to go two three or four
four thank you Heidi so if it's your
turn which one my friend would you
like
Skyler and would you like 24 or 10
10 and where would you like it to go two
or three two thanks Sophia and Simon
which my friends would you like Jordan
Jordan I'm going like one or 15 one I'm
going try something a little bit
different with you would you like to put
it in the last position or swap it out
for another
one taking my position he's taking my
position okay
thanks
Simon now let's look at the drawings you
didn't use as you can see they're all
different we've got things like Lego
dragons we've got Burgers so they're all
different yeah yes let's look at the
drawings you did choose you chose a
snake a slice of
[Music]
lime a
house and some
mountains each of you had a free choice
of which dra you wanted and more
importantly where to put
it the snake looks like an S the lime
looks like a c the house looks like an A
and the mountains look like an M that's
why the word scam right right yeah I
said though we're going to create a
brand new magic word that can be our
magic
word everyone shouts scam as loud as
they can on the count of three one 2 3
[Applause]
SC but what if I told you that we knew
what the magic world would be before we
even picked
it at the beginning of my ACT I gave you
each a drawing to hold on to I like to
take the drawing out of the envelope and
show it to
everyone as you can see they
match
now as well as I'm something on the
front of their t-shirt my friends also
had something on the back
look word equals scam
wow now look okay so I'm at AGT I'm
going to go in do what I need to do get
out as fast as I can okay let's go I
can't believe I'm actually inside the
AGT theater right there's a desk better
be quick can't get
caught what is he doing some there oh
God some's going to hate
this what's that
oh now you probably were doing what I
did at the death assignment well
hopefully you're not too
mad watch
[Music]
this wa it's a scam everywhere look scam
scam scam scam scam scam
SC sorry
Simon
wa hello hello what's your name Magic
Mike Jacobson Magic Mike Jacobson so
you're going to be doing magic that's
right well what a coincidence to have
that name and to be doing what
yeah the movie was Lucy based on my life
okay how long have you been doing magic
I like did Magic everywhere I could from
like my home to barber shops and
everywhere in between and eventually
kind of just like rose and Rose and Rose
and the love you keep doing it you know
so this perfect okay and how old are you
uh 36 36 and where are you from LA and
what how do you make a living do you
make a living doing magic uh no uh not
yet I work in advertising by day but um
this performance will determine whether
I can quit
oh so we'll see what happens no pressure
yeah no big deal but actually a huge
deal for me well let's see what you do
are you nervous exactly let's see yeah
I'm a little nervous I'm also just
excited to be here we'll wish you the
best of luck buddy thank you go
ahead I'm going to share something with
you all tonight that every magician has
but no magician will show you for some
reason
it's this it's an invisible deck of
cards uh it's a bit hard to see in this
light
um so what I'm going to do is I'm going
to burn the invisible deck from 52 all
the way down to one at the end Simon
you're going to be a hero as you always
are in my heart and you're going to save
one of the remaining cards from Bernie
but it depends on what Heidi and Sophia
decide Heidi take that match
I don't want you to strike it and stare
into the
flame let's just say there's two groups
number cards and face cards we need to
decide whether you want to start the
burn all the numbers or all the
faces blow it out when you're ready am I
telling you yes please all the
faces the faces are now on the fire you
can pass the box over to
Sophia Sophia take your match
okay left in the fire we got Jacks
Queens Kings okay the only way to divide
those up would be yeah men and
women we need to burn that
match and tell us do you want to burn
all the men do you want to burn all the
women to a crisp oh the men that was a
very quick decision you go ahead you
blow it
out and you can pass that to
Simon you're going to save one of the
remaining cards for Burnie all we have
left are the Four Queens
Queen of Hearts Queen of Spades Queen of
Clubs Queen of
Diamonds going to light that
match and whenever you're ready blow it
out I want you to draw with that match
the suit of the queen that you want to
save Hearts Spades clubs or
diamonds is that a diamond here's the
thing are you
sure Simon if you shake the matchbox do
you hear something in
there open that up for us because in all
of your hands the entire time there's
been nothing
but one
card sitting inside there protected by a
paperclip my sure singed like a spined a
bit of a fire you guys could have saved
whatever you wanted to but you and you
and you decided
together Sav the Queen of Diamonds
thank you thank you very
much thank
you I appreciate that very much but this
is America's Got Talent I'm here to take
this to the next level and so how I
don't know if you noticed but there's an
invisible deck of cards right next to
your cup how if you would I want you to
just Shuffle the deck for me
please you might want to uh take it out
of the box
first thank you stupid me great and now
feel free to show off all your shuffling
skills just make sure it's really mixed
oh my god oh wow that was very
impressive he's so good
how now howwi what I want you to do is
just fan out the deck to yourself and
pick out any card you want don't don't
show me but remember it make sure
everyone can see it great how if there's
an invisible Sharpie right next to your
cup sign the back of the card for me
just with your first name
okay great I don't want to see it and
now take the card slide it right back in
put that all back in the box and then
throw it right back up to me whenever
you're ready perfect now
you just just minor Miracles it's fine
Howie you shuffled the deck you picked a
card you all saw it for the very first
time what's the card that you picked 10
of clubs I want to clarify something you
and I have never met correct never
nobody came up to you before the show
said anything for the very first time I
to open this up you said the T of clubs
cor I did because every single card in
here is face up except for
one uhoh one card with a signature on it
Howie can you confirm is that your
signature it is will you flip that over
for me are you kidding
me is that your
card thank you very much
that's
crazy thank you thank
you and he kept all his clothes
on Heidi what do you think I mean the
audience was so quiet I haven't heard
this audience this quiet all day I mean
we were all like like hanging by every
word that was coming out of your mouth
and it was incredible thank you very
much thank you really cool I'm like
mesmerized it was like fantastic and it
was funny at the beginning also with the
invisible part good job thank
you I'm going to make a prediction no
more advertising jobs for you cuz this
is what I think you were born to do
genuinely thank you
yes thank you so much I got to say and
you know people at home are always
skeptical because I think I I I swear to
you nobody here was in on this this is
my signature that was incredible I loved
it you know I think it was really good
and I think you're really good I'm going
to start the voting with the yes it's a
yes for me too Sophia yes and Simon for
yes thank you thank you guys so much
thank you thank you thank you thank you
very
much magic M oh my god listen how are
you feeling tell me I feel amazing I
feel like I've had so much stress all
day and now I feel like so punched that
is crazy that's my signature too is it
your signature it is my
signature that's crazy to it is
crazy I know I want to keep
this